myrepospace.com 2013-06-05

# MyRepoSpace.com - Terms of Service

The Privacy Policy, in conjunction with the Terms of Service, is collectively known as the "Agreement". 

MyRepoSpace will modify the Agreement which will become effective immediately upon posting on the website. Your continued use of the website and any associated services indicates your acceptance of the most recently posted Agreement. 

Any Content uploaded by you to MyRepoSpace becomes published Content and is not considered personally identifiable information subject to this Privacy Policy. 

MyRepoSpace will collect and store your IP Address to identify trends and provide functionality to the website. 

MyRepoSpace will never sell content submitted to MyRepoSpace. 

A cookie is a piece of data stored on your hard drive which contains data used for the MyRepoSpace website. Cookies will be used on MyRepoSpace to enhance the website's experience. Cookies contain such information login information that is used to store your session. 

You can choose not to use Cookies to store your login information by unchecking "Keep me Logged" on login.   
Cookies contain sensitive data, and can result in misuse. Cookies are encrypted, however do not guarantee that your login information is safe. You agree to take the risk when using cookies to store your login information. 

Cookies may be collected from Advertisers to further enhance your web browser experience 

We will NEVER rent, sell or share your information with third parties. However, we may disclose your personal information or any of its log file information when required by law or in the good-faith belief that such actions are necessary to: conform to the edicts of the law or comply with a legal process served on us; protect and defend the rights or property of MyRepoSpace, or visitors of MyRepoSpace; identify persons who may be violating the law, the legal notice, or the rights of third parties; co-operate with the investigations of purported unlawful activities. 

We will never send unsolicited (SPAM) emails to your registered email address. MyRepoSpace will only send email to your email address when: 

a) Verifying the existence of your email address   
b) When you receive a new comment on your profile, a package you host, etc.   
c) Website notice emails, for example, when major new changes on the website are being rolled out, or service outages will be experiences.   
d) Important account related events occur. 

You may choose to unsubscribe from ALL email contact on the settings page found here. 

Third-party websites or services linked to MyRepoSpace are not covered by this Privacy Policy. These websites may collect personally or non-personally identifiable information about you and place a cookie on your browser. MyRepoSpace is not responsible for the privacy practices of the third-party websites and companies. 

MyRepoSpace is not responsible if you volunteer personal information online that is accessible to the public. You may receive unsolicited messages from other parties or it may be used in a manner that violates the law, your personal privacy or your safety. By submitting such information, you assume the risks and sole liability arising as a result of such information being displayed. 

Your PayPal Email Address will be stored on an unencrypted database for use with certain monetary features of myRepoSpace.com 

Although we strive to protect your personal information, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us, and you do so at your own risk. We do not ensure or warrant the security of databases that store your personal information.
